// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Noemi has memorized the 'Panatang Makabayan' (Patriotic Oath) since her elementary days. She always recites it during the morning ceremonies before the class starts. Reciting this oath is an example of this speech style.",
    answer: "C. frozen",
    options: [
      "A. consultative",
      "B. formal",
      "C. frozen",
      "D. intimate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Marcus was tasked to give a message in virtual moving-up ceremonies. The said situation is an example of this speech style.",
    answer: "D. intimate",
    options: [
      "A. consultative",
      "B. formal",
      "C. frozen",
      "D. intimate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "These are the considerations in achieving communicative competence.",
    answer: "D. all of the above",
    options: [
      "A. a and b only",
      "B. a and c only",
      "C. b and d only",
      "D. all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "This is characterized by considering the kinds of audience and situations or environment in which the communication takes place.",
    answer: "C. speech context",
    options: [
      "A. communicative strategy",
      "B. speech act",
      "C. speech context",
      "D. speech style"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Every morning, Sarah faces the mirror and talks to herself asking what clothes to wear for the day, what food to eat and what things to do. This scenario is one of the many typical samples of this type of speech context.",
    answer: "B. Intrapersonal",
    options: [
      "A. Interpersonal",
      "B. Intrapersonal",
      "C. public",
      "D. all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "This type of speech context requires interaction with a small number of individuals.",
    answer: "A. interpersonal",
    options: [
      "A. interpersonal",
      "B. intrapersonal",
      "C. public",
      "D. all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "You were part of a student council campaign and were asked to prepare a 3-minute rebuttal speech on the issue of cyber-bullying. As an advocate, you spoke in front of everybody during the meeting-de-avance. This scenario is one of the many types of this speech context.",
    answer: "C. public",
    options: [
      "A. interpersonal",
      "B. intrapersonal",
      "C. public",
      "D. all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "This type of speech style occurs between and among family members.",
    answer: "D. intimate",
    options: [
      "A. casual",
      "B. consultative",
      "C. formal",
      "D. intimate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "This type of speech style happens between and among friends and acquaintances.",
    answer: "A. casual",
    options: [
      "A. casual",
      "B. consultative",
      "C. formal",
      "D. intimate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Danica asked Olivia, 'Have you talked to Ms. De Leon about our project?' The possible perlocutionary effect of this question is shown in this act.",
    answer: "D. Olivia approaches Ms. De Leon regarding the project.",
    options: [
      "A. Olivia gets upset with Danica for the reminder.",
      "B. Danica urges Olivia to converse with Ms. De Leon.",
      "C. Ms. De Leon accepts Olivia and Danicaâ€™s project.",
      "D. Olivia approaches Ms. De Leon regarding the project."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The teacher, due to modular distance learning delivery, has asked for the mobile numbers, email, or social media accounts and other contact information of the students. The corresponding illocutionary act of the utterance, 'May I have your contact details please?' is this.",
    answer: "D. Request",
    options: [
      "A. Beg",
      "B. Demand",
      "C. Insist",
      "D. Request"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "This aspect of the speech act refers to the utterance of the speaker to a specific situation for an intended discourse impact.",
    answer: "A. Illocutionary",
    options: [
      "A. Illocutionary",
      "B. Locutionary",
      "C. personality",
      "D. perlocutionary"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "One day, Gina and Marissa saw one another along the corridors. Marissa smiled and waved her hand to Gina. Approaching, Gina said 'Hi! How are you?' This communication strategy is exemplified here.",
    answer: "C. repair",
    options: [
      "A. nomination",
      "B. topic-shifting",
      "C. repair",
      "D. turn-taking"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "This is the communication strategy that allows a smooth transition or shift from one topic to another.",
    answer: "B. topic-shifting",
    options: [
      "A. nomination",
      "B. topic-shifting",
      "C. repair",
      "D. turn-taking"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "To ensure that the topic is fully discussed and clarified, Mr. Cortez, the facilitator, tries his best to stir the conversation strictly within the confines of the agenda. This communication strategy is employed here by Mr. Cortez.",
    answer: "A. nomination",
    options: [
      "A. nomination",
      "B. repair",
      "C. topic-shifting",
      "D. turn-taking"
    ]
  },
];
